http://www.floweramacolumbus.com/about/policies/privacy-policy/

Voted top florist in Columbus...AGAIN.  Read about us in (614) Magazine 2020 COLUMBEST edition.
Home
Same Day Delivery in Greater Columbus
(614) 256-6646
Login
Cart (0)
Effective date: September 1, 2011
Your privacy is important to Flowerama Columbus ("we" or "us"). To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our privacy practices and the choices you can make about the ways in which information about you is collected and used at www.floweramacolumbus.com. We encourage you to read and review the terms of this Privacy Policy before using our Web site. By using our Web site, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Web site.
Information We Collect
Personally Identifiable Information
To fulfill your requests for information, enable you to participate in our offerings, and provide you with opportunities to learn about other products and services in which we think you might be interested, we ask that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, and date of birth. By providing your personal information on our Web site, you consent to allow us to use that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
In some instances, we may request that you submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address; or if you include references, you might submit the reference’s name and e-mail address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.
Any information you disclose voluntarily on our Web site or in any forum and blogs that we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our Web site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the Internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Fire Fox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows Vista, Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, AT&T), the name of the Web pages you visit, the time you access our Web pages, and the length of time you stay on those pages.
We collect this information in order to determine which areas of our Web site are most popular and to enhance your experience with our Web site. This information may also be shared with third parties on an aggregate and non-personally identifiable basis. However, please be assured that this information will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors of our Web site.
Our Web site uses Google Analytics or other third party web analytics service. Such service may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this Web site. The service does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this Web site. The service does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use the service.
How We Use the Information
We use your personally identifiable information to provide the requested information or content, respond to your inquiries about our offerings, offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, or for other purposes disclosed at the time of collection. We also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our products or services, or regarding changes to our Privacy Policy, or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of our Web site or our products and services. In addition, we may use such information to improve the content and navigation of our Web site, or for other internal purposes.
We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or information. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.
We may combine the information we collect with information available from other sources, including information received from promotional partners or other third parties. Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
Information Sharing
We may, from time to time, share personally identifiable information with other companies affiliated with us and unrelated third parties (e.g., retailers, marketers) to enable them to provide users with opportunities to learn of products or services in which they may be interested. You should also be aware that this means that we may transfer information to any country in the world, including the United States and other countries that may not offer the same level of data protection as the country where you reside. Please see the "Your Choices" section below for more information on how you can express your preferences regarding our sharing of information.
We also may disclose personally identifiable information in the following instances:
Legal Action: We may disclose information about our users, including personally identifiable information, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web site or applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web site. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users.
Corporate Change: We may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, asset sale, or other corporate change or combination of assets involving us.
In addition, we may disclose anonymous, aggregated user statistics to third parties for a variety of purposes. For example, we may disclose how many individuals visited certain areas of our Web site, how many men or women receive our newsletter, or other demographic data about users of our products or services.
Your Choices
As noted above, we may use the personally identifiable information we collect from you to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of e-mail communications or by logging into your account and changing your communication preferences.
As also noted above, we may, from time to time, share personally identifiable information with companies whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., other marketers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. To request that we not share your information for such marketing purposes, you may log into your profile and change your account preferences accordingly or contact us using the information at the bottom of this page
Cookies
To enhance your experience with our site, many of our Web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.
Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the website that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer. However, please be aware that some features of our Web site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. We do not control cookies that you may occasionally get from third-party sites.
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
We may, from time to time, offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties, including affiliated businesses. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information. Since these third parties will use your information in accordance with their own privacy practices, you should check their websites for information regarding their privacy policies. We will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.
We may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our Web pages. These third-party ad servers may use cookies, Web beacons, clear .gifs, or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third-party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.
We and our advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site and to conduct research about the advertisements.
Links to Other Sites
Our site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us and whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.
Our Commitment to Data Security
We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to, maintain security of, and correctly use the information we collect. Personally identifiable information and account activity are also protected through the use of e-mail addresses and passwords. In order to maintain the security of your information, you should protect the confidentiality of such information used to log into your account. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.
How You Can Access and Update Information
If you have previously provided any personally identifiable information to us by way of our Web site, you retain the right to review, correct, update, delete or otherwise modify such information.
To access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you that we maintain, or to correct factual errors in such information, simply log into your account using your e-mail address and password to update your information. Or you may also contact us at the “Contact” address, telephone number or e-mail provided below.To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
International Visitors
Information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States where our central database is operated. The privacy laws of the U.S. may not be as comprehensive as the data protection laws of the European Union and elsewhere. Please be assured that we take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected and implement necessary measures on an ongoing basis to keep your personal information secure. By providing us with your personally identifiable information, you consent to its use in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including the transfer of personally identifiable information relating to you to our computer systems in the United States.
Privacy Policy for Minors
We do not knowingly collect information from minors. If you are under the age of 18, we request that you do not provide any personally identifiable information to us.
Updates to This Privacy Policy
From time to time, we reserve the right to make updates to this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by, for example, placing a notice on our Web site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of our Web site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such change.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at:
Phone 1-866-937-6355 or 614-256-6646Fax 614-575-8017US Mail Flowerama Columbus6311 East Main StreetReynoldsburg, OH 43068
Local Flower Shops
Stop in and visit one of our Flowerama Columbus locations listed below!
Columbus Flower Shop614.547.0808
The Columbus location opened December 16th, 2005 at the corner of Morse and Karl road. The store manager's names are Jenny and Tina and they have more then 10 years of floral experience.
This location offers same day delivery to all of Greater Columbus Cities including the following: Columbus, Dublin, Grandview Heights, Hilliard, OSU Campus, Upper Arlington and more. 1600 Morse RoadColumbus, OH 43229Get Directions »
Reynoldsburg Flower Shop614.575.2070
The Reynoldsburg location opened June 23, 1990 at the corner of Brice and Main. The store manager's name is Lisa and she has more then 20 years of managerial experience.
This location offers same day delivery to all of Greater Columbus Cities including the following: Reynoldsburg, Pickerington, Pataskala, Obetz, Groveport, Grove City, Columbus, Canal Winchester and more6311 East Main StreetReynoldsburg, OH 43068Get Directions »
Westerville Flower Shop614.898.9588
The Westerville store opened its doors on May 25, 1996 at the corner of Schrock Road and State Street. The store manager's name is Jenny and she has more then 20 years floral experience.
This location offers same day delivery to all of Greater Columbus cities including the following: Westerville, Worthington, New Albany, Gahanna, Minerva Park, Easton, Columbus, Powell, Columbus Airport635 South State StreetWesterville, OH 43081Get Directions »
Whitehall Flower Shop614.759.1517
The Whitehall location opened January 27, 1995 at the corner of Broad and Hamilton. The store manager's name is Jaime and she has more then 15 years of floral experience.
This location offers same day delivery to all of Greater Columbus Cities including the following: Whitehall, Columbus, Bexley, Downtown Columbus, Minerva Park, Hilltop and more4785 East Broad StreetWhitehall, OH 43213Get Directions »
Same Day Flower Delivery
Bexley
Canal Winchester
Clintonville
Columbus
Columbus Airport
Downtown Columbus
Dublin
Occasions
AnniversaryBestsellersBirthdayChristmasFall SplendorFlowersGet WellHanukkahHospitalsJust for KidsLove & RomanceNew BornOhio StatePlant CollectionSympathy
Westerville
635 South State Street
Westerville, OH 43081
Reynoldsburg
6311 East Main Street
Reynoldsburg, OH 43068
Whitehall
4785 East Broad Street
© 2020 Flowerama Columbus.
All rights reserved.Web Design & Development by m2 marketing & Emerald City Websites
